One of the problems damaging our planet is the number of things we throw away.
破坏地球的问题之一，就是我们丢弃的物品数量过多。
Rubbish of all kinds is piling up in landfill and polluting our rivers and oceans.
各类垃圾在垃圾填埋场堆积如山，还污染了我们的河流与海洋。
A more recent addition to the list of things we chuck away is e-waste – electronic items that are broken and not recycled.
在我们丢弃的物品清单里，最近又多了电子垃圾这类东西——也就是那些损坏后未被回收的电子产品。
Now solutions are being found to give this stuff a new life.
如今，人们已经找到了一些办法，能让这些东西重获新生。
Many millions of tonnes of televisions, phones, and other electronic equipment are discarded each year, partly because it’s cheaper to replace them than fix them, but also because we lack the skills to repair them.
每年有数百万吨的电视机、手机以及其他电子设备被丢弃，部分原因是更换这些设备比维修更便宜，同时也因为我们缺乏维修它们的技能。
A UN report claims the 50 million tonnes of e-waste generated every year will more than double to 110 million tonnes by 2050, making it the fastest growing waste stream in the world.
联合国的一份报告指出，目前每年产生的5000万吨电子垃圾，到2050年将增加一倍以上，达到1.1亿吨，电子垃圾也因此成为全球增长最快的垃圾种类。
However, there’s a growing trend for repair events and clubs which could be part of a solution to the growing amount of electrical and electronic junk.
不过，修理活动和修理俱乐部的风潮正在兴起，这或许能成为解决电子垃圾日益增多问题的途径之一。
The BBC visited a Restart Project in London, which is one of many found around the world.
英国广播公司探访了伦敦的一个“重启计划”，这类计划在全球多地都有开展。
One of its volunteers, Francesco Calo, said that "this project allows you to reduce waste, extend the life of objects, and it helps people who cannot afford to get rid of items that have developed a fault."
该计划的志愿者弗朗西斯科·卡洛表示：“这个计划既能减少垃圾，延长物品的使用寿命，还能帮助那些无力更换故障物品的人。”
As many electrical items contain valuable metals, another idea is e-waste mining.
由于许多电子产品都含有贵金属，另一种处理方式应运而生，那就是电子垃圾提炼。
An experiment at the University of New South Wales involves extracting these materials from electronic gadgets.
新南威尔士大学开展了一项实验，从电子设备中提取这些金属材料。
It’s thought that doing this could be more profitable than traditional mining.
人们认为，这种提炼方式可能比传统采矿更有利可图。
With phones typically containing as many as 60 elements, this could be part of the solution to our appetite for new technology.
通常一部手机就含有多达60种元素，电子垃圾提炼或许能在一定程度上满足我们对新技术产品的需求。
These projects make total sense - collections of e-waste for recycling are “stagnating or even decreasing” according to Ruediger Kuehr, of the United Nations University.
这些计划的意义重大——联合国大学的吕迪格·库尔表示，电子垃圾的回收量正“处于停滞状态，甚至在下降”。
And in countries where there is no legislation, much of it just gets dumped.
在那些没有相关立法的国家，大部分电子垃圾都被直接丢弃。
However, the European Union, for example, is trying to tackle the problem by insisting manufacturers have to make appliances longer-lasting and will have to supply spare parts for machines for up to 10 years.
不过，以欧盟为例，它正着手解决这个问题，强制要求制造商生产更耐用的家电产品，并且在最高可达10年的时间里必须为产品提供零配件。